SARAH TRUONG

UI/UX Designer

struongux.com

struong428@gmail.com

813.810.9913

EDUCATION

A.S. Graphic & Interactive Design

Valencia College Sep 2015 - Dec 2017 Orlando, FL

B.S. Microbiology

University of Georgia Aug 2011 - May 2015 Athens, GA

Zell Miller Scholarship

SKILLS

Design

Adobe Suite Sketch Balsamiq InVision Prototyping Web Design User Research

Usability Testing

A/B Testing

Development

HTML 5 / CSS 3 Basic Javascript Jquery

Digital Marketing

Email Marketing Basic SEO MailChimp Google Analytics

LEADERSHIP

Co-President

UGA Japan Club 2013 - 2014

ABOUT ME

I am a UI/UX designer that is design, data, and user driven. With a background in both science and interactive design, I strive to create innovative solutions to better user experiences through aesthetics and problem-solving. Willing to relocate.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI/UX Designer

ConnectWise

Oct 2019 - Present | Tampa, FL

- Refine user experiences and design wireframes, mockups, and interactive prototypes for software and mobile apps
- Perform user research and usability sessions with key stakeholders and partners

Digital Designer

Westgate Resorts

Jul 2018 - Present | Orlando, FL

- Designed marketing collateral and high-fidelity prototypes for website redesigns to increase conversions
- Established design library and improved design process and workflow for projects to make production more efficient

UI Designer

StrategyBeam

Oct 2018 - Feb 2019 | Orlando, FL

- · Created digital assets, wireframes, and mock-ups for website
- Provided UI solutions to business goals to increase conversion rates and leads for website redesigns

Web Design Intern

Ripley Entertainment

Feb 2018 - Aug 2018 | Orlando, FL

- Redesigned and optimized WordPress websites to ensure a positive user experience through design and functionality
- Designed email newsletters for email marketing and digital assets for social media marketing, ads & promotions

Freelancer

Self-employed

June 2016 - July 2017 | Orlando, FL

- Consulted with local businesses to provide design solutions and solve users' needs through user research, information design, interaction design, visual design and prototyping
- Created marketing collateral posters, banners, menus, pamphlets, photo editing, responsive web layouts, user studies and UI designs